Guide to the Wayne P. Ellis Collection of Kodakiana, 1886-1989 and undated
Wayne P. Ellis Collection of Kodakiana 1886-1989 and undated
- Periodicals Series, 1907-1985 and undated
  - Contents of Box: (Box 36)
    - Kodak Camera Club News
      - [cover with sunlight effect], [circa 1970], [cover with child's face], [ca. 1975]
    - Kodak Dealer-Finisher News
      For professional sales staff. Contains advance information on the new Kodak Instamatic Camera and Kodapak Film Cartridges, with parts breakdown, selling-point highlights, reasoning behind the products, promotional signs to purchase, and questions and answers about the products.
      - April 1963
    - Kodak International Photography
      For professional photographers. Contents include photographs from professional international photographers; essays on specific photographers; and articles on photographic exhibits, types of commercial photography (record jackets), and types of camera.
      - 10 (1974)
    - Kodak Magazine for the Graphics Professional
      For professional photographers. Contains informational articles on photography (halftones, phototypesetting, etc.), and information on Kodak products, trade shows, etc.
      - 3 (1985)
    - Kodak News (by 1954 entitled Kodak Dealer News)
      For professional sales staff. Contains advance notice of new Kodak products; information on promotional items, contests, displays; and sales ideas (TV ads, showing related accessories, etc.).
      - 35:8 (Aug. 1949), 35:12 (Dec. 1949), 40:5-7 (June/July-Oct. 1954), 41:3-4 (Mar.-May 1955)
  - Contents of Box: (Box 37)
    - Kodak Photo
      For amateur photographers. Contains educational articles on photography (primarily color photography) in non-technical language; advertisements for Kodak products; many illustrative photographs; and section with suggestions for individuals about submitted photographs.
      - 1:1 (1946)
    - Kodak Photo Magazine
      For amateur photographers. Contains many articles on photography (mounting in albums, seasonal photography, series shots, indoor v. outdoor lighting, etc.); many illustrative photographs; information about new Kodak products; and "Good Shots" section with amateur photographs.
      - Fall 1946, Holiday 1946, Feb./Mar. 1947, Fall 1947
    - Kodak Photo News
      For amateurs. Contains primarily detailed information on new Kodak products and shows (including "Profile '76," a multimedia show focusing on people across the country for the bicentennial), also "Tear-Out Tips" on photography.
      - 1975:2-3, 1976:1, 1976:3, 1983:1, 1985:1
    - Kodak Trade Circular
      For professional sales personnel, labeled "Confidential-For Trade Circulation Only-Read and file for future reference." Contains information on new and discontinued Kodak products, price changes, advance information about Kodak ads and promotions, display window and sales suggestions.
      - 24:4 (Apr. 1923), Index for 30 (Jan.-Dec. 1929), 39:1 (Jan. 1938), 39:10 (Oct. 1938), 42:1 (Jan. 1941), 43:11-12 (Nov.-Dec. 1942)
    - New England Photographer
      For professional photographers. Contains professional articles (doretype processing, darkroom efficiency, fluorescent lighting), many advertisements for Kodak products, and commercial articles (training apprentices, boosting business. etc/)
      - 19:3 (Jan./Feb. 1941)
    - The Photo Finisher
      For professional photographers (finishers). Contains advance information on new Kodak products, services, and promotions with ordering information; professional articles (hot weather finishing, copying photographs, coloring photos, etc.); and commercial articles ( advertising, keeping agents interested).
      - 3:3 (July 1929), 3:7 (Nov. 1929), 3:9 (Jan. 1930), 3:11 (Mar. 1930), 4:2 (June 1930), 5:1 (Jan. 1931), 5:7 (July 1931), 5:11 (Nov. 1931), 6:3 (Apr./May 1932), 7:2-3 (Mar.-Apr. 1934), 8:3 (Apr. 1935), 8:5 (June 1935), 9:1 (Jan. 1936), 10:3-5 (Apr.-Sept. 1937), 11:6 (Nov./Dec. 1938), 12:2 (Mar. 1939), 13:2 (Mar. 1940), 15:1 (Jan./Feb. 1942), 20:5 (Nov. 1948)
    - Photographic Review/Photographic Digest
      For professional photographers. Contains many ads for Kodak photographic products, information on conventions, commercial articles (national advertising, training apprentices, gift certificates), professional articles (hot weather fixing, focusing wide angle lenses), joke page entitled "Retouching Some Old Ones." Regionally published magazine with slightly differing cover design, but virtually identical contents. Titles vary with region.
      - Photographic Review: (Chicago, Ill.)
        - 4:12 (June 1926)
      - Photographic Review: (Jacksonville, Fla.)
        - [vol. page cut off] (June/July 1938)
      - Photographic Digest: (Philadelphia)
        - 6:4 (Oct. 1927), 8:7 (Jan. 1930), 9:6 (Dec. 1930), 9:11 (May 1931), 10:1 (July 1931), 11:7 (Jan. 1933), 11:10 (Apr. 1933)
      - Photographic Digest: (San Francisco)
        - 16:4 (Feb./Mar. 1938)
    - Tech Bits
      For professional scientists and engineers. Contains highlights of Kodak products and articles on photography topics (cleaning plates, washing photographic materials, making microscopic reticles, splicing films, etc.). Technical language used throughout and illustrated with many graphs.
      - 1963:3, 1964:1-4, 1965:2, 1966:1-4, 1968:2-3, 1969:1, 1969:4
- Product Catalogs Series, 1890-1985 and undated
  Contains a variety of catalogs describing a wide array of photographic products. Audiences are both professional persons and the general public. Arranged chronologically within folders or boxes.
  - Kodak Product Catalogs Subseries, 1890-1985 and undated
    - Contents of Box: (Box 38)
      - Multi-product catalogs, 1890-1916, (26 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 39)
      - Multi-product catalogs, 1917-1931, (21 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 40)
      - Multi-product catalogs, 1932-1955, (34 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 41)
      - Multi-product catalogs (oversize), 1931, 1955, 1961, 1966, 1971-1973, undated, (9 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 42)
      - Cine-Kodak equipment catalogs (oversize), 1927-1941, 1946-1947, 1950, 1957, undated, (59 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 43)
      - Kodascope Library catalogs 1924-1938, (9 items)
      - Kodascope Library Review, undated, (2 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 44)
      - Kodak schools, teaching guides, contests, 1905-1980, (12 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 45)
      - Multi-product catalogs for graphic arts professionals (oversize), 1910-1985 and undated, (14 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 46)
      - Materials for the graphic arts (oversize), 1948-1967 and undated, (7 items)
      - Photographic products catalogs (oversize), 1977-1983 and undated, (4 items)
      - Kodak Products for the Professional (oversize), 1953-1974, (6 items)
  - Non-Kodak Product Catalogs Subseries, circa 1860-1972 and undated
    - Contents of Box: (Box 47)
      - Ansco, 1906-1918 and undated, (4 items)
      - E. and H. T. Anthony, [1860?]-1891, (3 items)
      - Blair Camera, 1895-1911, (10 items)
      - Borsum Camera, 1900
      - Burke and Ames; (Rexo Camera), undated
      - Calumet Photographic, [1970?], (4 items)
      - Camera Place, undated
      - Canadian Card Company, 1907, 1911, (2 items)
      - Central Camera, 1930-1938, (3 items)
      - Century Camera, 1901-1910, (4 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 48)
      - Commercial Camera Company; (Photostat Camera), undated
      - Conley Camera Company; (Kewpie Camera), undated
      - Dallmeyer, undated, (4 items)
      - Elko, 1942
      - GAF Corporation, 1972, (2 items)
      - Gundalch Optical; (Korona Camera), 1899-1915, (7 items)
      - Hasselblad, [1966?], undated, (2 items)
      - Horne, Thornwaite and Wood, 1890
      - Ilex Optical, undated
      - International Photo Sales Company; (Ipsco Camera), undated, (2 items)
      - Manhattan Optical, 1895-1900, (3 items)
      - Minox, undated
      - George Murphy, Inc., 1900-1932, (3 items)
      - Photo Printer Manufacturing Company, undated
      - James W. Queen and Company, 1892
      - Ray Camera, 1898, 1900, (2 items)
      - Riley Brothers, 1896-1897
    - Contents of Box: (Box 49)
      - Scovill Manufacturing Company, 1883
      - Seneca Camera, 1904-1925, undated, (13 items)
      - Solar Cine Products, 1970-1972, (3 items)
      - Stirn and Lyon, reprint, undated
      - Sunart Photo, 1896
      - Vives Camera Company, 1901
      - Voigtlander, [1906?]-[1910?], undated, (7 items)
      - Wollensak Optical, 1919, undated, (2 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 50)
      - American Optical (oversized), [1946?]
      - E. and H. T. Anthony (oversized), 1896
      - Bausch and Lomb Optical (oversized), 1913
      - Bell and Howell; (Filmo Camera, oversized), 1939
      - Burke and James (oversized), 1969
      - Calumet Manufacturing (oversized), 1966
      - Central Camera Company (oversized), undated
      - Century Camera (oversized, plus close-ups of cover), 1905, (2 items)
      - Graflex (oversized), 1967, undated, (7 items)
      - Andrew Lloyd and Company (oversized), [1901?]
      - Montgomery Ward (oversized), 1898-1952, (3 items)
      - Photo-Porst (oversized), [ca. 1937]
      - Rieztschel (oversized), 1909, undated, (2 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 51)
      - Premo; (Rochester Optical Company) catalogs, 1890-1909, (26 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 52)
      - Premo catalogs, 1910-1922, (18 items)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 53)
      - Graflex ( Folmer and Schwing Division of Kodak), 1907-1929, 1935, 1940, 1956, 1967, and undated, (30 items)
- Kodak Products Leaflets Series, 1912-1989 and undated
  Ephemeral publications promoting a variety of Kodak products, including cameras, lenses, photographic papers and films, darkroom equipment, and photography albums. Arranged by date within folders.
  - Contents of Box: (Box 54)
    - Kodak Instamatic, 1963, 1969, 1974, (3 items)
    - Kodak Signet 40, 1953, 1956, (4 items)
    - Kodak Retina Cameras, 1955, 1957, (3 items)
    - Kodak Medalist and Medalist II, 1941, 1947, 1949, (3 items)
    - Kodak Bantam Special, 1931, 1936, (3 items)
    - Continental Kodaks, 1930, undated, (2 items)
    - Kodak Ektra, undated
    - Super Kodak Six-20, undated
    - Kodak Brownie Cameras, 1958, 1962, (2 items)
    - Kodak Stereo Camera, 1957, (2 items)
    - Kodak Miniature Cameras, 1938, 1940, 1941, 1955, undated, (5 items)
    - Kodak Reflex, 1946
    - Kodak Tourist Cameras, 1949
    - Kodak 35mm Cameras, 1957
    - Kodak Movie Cameras, 1960, 1973, undated, (3 items)
    - Kodachrome, 1936, 1938, 1939, 1964, (4 items)
  - Contents of Box: (Box 55)
    - Eastman Professional Films, 1918, 1928, 1931-1933, 1936-1938, undated, (10 items)
    - Kodak Films, 1936, 1938, 1939, 1949, undated, (5 items)
    - Vitava Portrait Papers, 1925, 1930, undated, (4 items)
    - Eastman Plates, 1924, 1930, 1935-1938, undated, (8 items)
    - Eastman Photographic Papers, 1935
    - Velox Papers, 1912, 1915, 1922, 1928, 1934, undated, (7 items)
  - Contents of Box: (Box 56)
    - Eastman Professional Films, Plates and Papers, 1938, 1940, 1942, undated, (8 items)
    - Kodak Movie Projectors, 1941, 1953, 1954, 1964, 1936, undated, (6 items)
    - Kodak Slide Projectors, 1937, 1947-1950, 1952, 1954-1956, (11 items)
    - Kodak Filters, 1938, 1940, 1946-1947, 1954, (6 items)
    - Lens Attachments, undated, (2 items)
    - Kodak Albums, 1948
    - Kodak Enlarging Equipment, 1941-1942, 1945, 1948-1950, undated, (10 items)
    - Kodak Pola-Lights, 1949
    - Kodak Darkroom Equipment, 1947-1948, undated, (4 items)
    - Kodak Accessories, 1951, 1964, (2 items)
    - Eastman X-Ray Materials and Accessories, 1922
    - Kodak Programs for Home Viewing, 1979, 1989, undated, (3 items)
    - Guide to Kodak How-To Books, 1974
  - Contents of Box: (Box 57)
    - Kodachrome and Kodacolor from All Angles (book), 1942
    - Kodachrome and Ektachrome from All Angles (book), 1949
    - Miscellaneous oversized leaflets, 1948, 1950, 1959, 1966, 1984, (5 items)
- Photography Manuals Series, [circa 1890]-1987 and undated
  Pamphlets, bound volumes, and audio-visual publications aimed chiefly at amateur photographers, although some are also directed at professionals. Includes both general reference works and works relating to specific photographic techniques such as flash photography and portraits. Many of these publications are connected with specific equipment. Arranged in chronological order within folders or boxes.
  - Amateur/General Public Subseries, 1898-1987 and undated
    - General Topics
      - Contents of Box: (Box 58)
        - How to Make Good Pictures, 1912, 1928, 1935-1940, (7 items)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 59)
        - How to Make Good Pictures, 1941, 1943, (6 items)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 60)
        - How to Make Good Pictures, 1951-1952, 1957, 1967, 1972, 1981, (6 items)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 61)
        - How to Make Good Pictures, undated, (6 items) (includes one copy in Spanish)
        - Picture Taking and Picture Making, 1898 (5th and 7th editions), (2 items)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 62)
        - Picture Taking and Picture Making, 1898 (8th and 11th editions), (2 items)
        - How to Make Good Movies, [1953?], (2 items)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 63)
        - How to Make Good Home Movies, 1958-1966, (3 items)
        - Junior Scenarios for Home Movies, 1928
        - Home Movies Made Easy, 1970
        - How to Make Good Sound Movies, 1973
        - Better Movies in Minutes, 1972
        - Maintaining Your Still and Movie Camera and Projector, 1975
        - Kodak Pocket Guide to Video, 1987
      - Contents of Box: (Box 64)
        - The Modern Way in Picture Making, 1905, 1907
        - The Fundamentals of Photography, 1928
        - At Home with Your Kodak, [1935?]
        - The Modern Kodak - How to Make the Most of It, [1928?], (4 items)
        - Photography, 1937, 1942, (2 folders)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 65)
        - The Way to Better Pictures, undated
        - Photography Simplified, 1938
        - Photography in Wartime, 1944
        - What to Photograph, 1945
        - X-Rays and You, 1948
        - Photo Tips, 1950
        - The Kodak Camera Guide, 1959
        - The Here's How Book of Photography, 1971
        - The Here's How Book of Photography, vol. 2, 1977
        - Kodak Master Photoguide, 1981
        - Kodak Pocket Guide to Great Picture Taking, 1984
      - Contents of Box: (Box 66)
        - Kodak Reference Handbook, 1940-1949, [1943?], 1948, (3 items)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 67)
        - Kodak Photographic Handbook, [1952?], [1964?], [1973?], (3 items)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 68)
        - Kodak Information Book, 1943
        - The Joy of Photography, 1979
        - More Joy of Photography, 1981
        - What You Can do With a Kodak, undated
    - Specific Topics
      - Contents of Box: (Box 69)
        - About Lenses, 1921-1922, 1923, 1925, (4 items)
        - Artura Results, undated, 8th, 9th, 17th, 19th eds., (4 items)
        - Cine-Kodak, 1923-1924, 1928, 1931-1932, 1936, 1946, undated, (15 items)
        - Kodak Films, 1947, 1952-1954, 1956, 1975, 1978, (8 items)
        - Seed Plates, undated
        - Slide Showmanship with a Kodak Carousel Projector, 1975
        - Kodak Filters, 1956
        - Picture Taking at Night, 1935
        - Let's Take Kodacolor Pictures, 1952
      - Contents of Box: (Box 70)
        - Enlarging, 1897, 1910, 1915, 1921-1922, 1924, 1926, 1934-1935, 1952, (10 items)
        - Kodascope, 1926-1927, 1929, 1932, 1934, 1937, 1945, (7 items)
        - Brownie Hawkeye Camera, 1952-1955, (4 items)
        - Kodak Duraflex II and III, 1952-1954, (5 items)
        - An Amateur Photoplay in the Making, [ca. 1927]
        - Flash Photography, 1915, 1917, 1965, (3 items)
        - Picture Taking with Still Cameras, 1948
        - Better Snapshots of Your Children, 1954
        - Travel Pictures, 1963
      - Contents of Box: (Box 71)
        - The Photography of Colored Objects, 1923, 1928, 1938, (3 items)
        - Kodak Guide to 35mm Photography, 1986
        - Photography by Polarized Light, 1938
        - How to Make Ten Dollars a Day with Your Kodak, 1926
        - Adventures in Existing-Light Photography, 1978
        - Kodak Pocket Guide to Sports Photography, 1984
        - Minitography and Cinetography, 1931
      - Contents of Box: (Box 72)
        - The Kodak Manual for No. 4 Folding Kodak, 1891
        - Printing, Developing and Enlarging, 1947-1948, 1982, (3 items)
        - Graphic Graflex Photography, 1944
        - Picturing the Times of Your Life, 1980
        - Picturing People, 1976
        - The Joy of Photographing People, 1983
    - Non-Kodak Product Manuals
      - Contents of Box: (Box 73)
        - Agfa/Ansco, 1943-1958, undated, (9 items)
        - Argus, 1954, undated, (3 items)
        - Bausch and Lomb, undated
        - DuPont Film, undated
        - Federal Manufacturing and Engineering Company, 1948
        - Flashlight Portraiture, 1912
        - General Electric, [1939?]
        - Kalart Company, 1955
        - Medo Photo Supply, undated
        - Sears, Roebuck and Company, undated, (4 items)
        - Sylvania Electric, 1954-1966, (3 items)
        - Practical Photography, 1919, 1923, (2 items)
        - Photography Outdoors, 1911
        - The New Photo-Miniature, [ca. 1890]
    - Audio-Visual Product Manuals (Kodak)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 74)
        - How to Process Color Negatives (audiocassette), 1975
        - How to Process Black and White Films and Prints (audiocassette), 1975
        - How to Process Color Prints (audiocassette), 1977
        - Introduction to Photography (videotape 101), 1985
        - Basic Picture-Taking (videotape 102), 1985
        - The Art of Photo Composition (videotape 103), 1985
        - Effective Use of Lenses (videotape 104), 1985
      - Contents of Box: (Box 75)
        - Existing-Light Photography (videotape 105), 1985
        - Photographers and Their Films (videotape 108), 1985
        - Prize-Winning Pictures (videotape 110), 1985
        - Action Photography (videotape 112), 1985
        - Advanced Existing-Light Photography (videotape 113), 1985
        - Scenic Photography (videotape 115), 1985
        - The Way I See It (videotape 116), 1985
        - Images with Imagination (videotape 123), 1985
        - Glamour Photography (videotape 124), 1985
        - Creating the Print (videotape 502), 1987
  - Trade and Technical Subseries(some non-Kodak) 1917-1980 and undated
    - Contents of Box: (Box 76)
      - From Dry Plates to Ektachrome Film, 1921
      - The Silver Bromide Grain of Photographic Emulsions, 1921
      - Gelatin in Photography, 1923
      - The Physics of the Developed Photographic Image, 1924
      - Motion Picture Laboratory Practice, 1936
    - Contents of Box: (Box 77)
      - Photographic Sensitometry, 1934
      - Photomicrography, 1944
      - Photographic Chemistry, 1980
      - Commercial Photo and Amateur Finishing, 1924?-1925?, 1935, 1938, (4 items)
      - Films, Plates and Papers for Commercial Photography, 1920, 1923, 1927, 1930, 1934-1935, 1937-1938, (8 items)
      - Color Printing with Wash-Off Relief Film, 1938-1939, (2 items)
      - Kodak Lenses for Professional Photography, 1951
      - Cinematographer's Field Guide, 1978
    - Contents of Box: (Box 78)
      - Book of Formulas for Professional Films and Plates, 1932-1934, 1937-1938, (5 items)
      - Kodacolor Portraiture, undated
      - X-Rays, 1922, 1924, 1929, 1933, 1936, (5 items)
      - Motion Picture Films, 1931, 1935, 1938-1939, 1942, 1945, 1947, (8 items)
      - Lantern Slides, 1919, 1927, (4 items)
      - Collodion and the Making of Wet Plate Negatives, 1929
      - Kodachrome Professional Film, 1941
      - Making Service Pictures for Industry, 1952
      - Photomicrography, 1932
      - Professional Enlarging, 1917-1918, 1926, (3 items)
      - Advice for Photographic Studios, 1927, undated, (2 items)
      - Stains on Negatives and Prints, 1938
      - Materials for the Construction of Photographic Processing Apparatus, 1929
    - Contents of Box: (Box 79)
      - A Way to Do It Better, [196-]
      - Photo Topics and Techniques, 1980
      - Clinical Photography, 1972
      - Photography from Light Planes and Helicopters, 1971
      - Ultraviolet and Fluorescence Photography, 1972
      - Photomicrography of Metals, 1971
      - Basic Scientific Photography, 1973
      - Photography in ..., 1954, (4 items)
      - Photographic Surveillance Techniques for Law Enforcement Agencies, 1972
      - High-Speed Photography in Product Development, 1955
      - Kodak Plates for Scientific and Technical Applications, 1968
      - Expand Applications of High Speed Photography, 1955
      - Incidental Intelligence About Kodak Resists, 1968, 1969
      - Promotional Programs for the Professional Studio, 1966
- Kodak Sales/Dealer Manuals Series, 1910s-1956 and undated
  Training materials for sales personnel and Kodak dealers. Arranged in chronological order within folders.
  - Contents of Box: (Box 80)
    - Sales/dealer manuals, [191-]-[194-], (7 items)
    - Promotional materials and catalogs for dealers, [194-]-[195-], (10 items)
    - Eastman Photographic Course for Salesmen, 1938-1944, (3 folders)
  - Contents of Box: (Box 81)
    - Conference notes from Kodak photographic sales training, 1956
    - Loose materials from notebook above, 1956
    - Eastman Reference Manual for Salesmen, [1937?]-[1941?]
- Other Kodak-Related Publications Series, 1888-1983 and undated
  Chiefly ephemeral non-serial publications related to Kodak products, company history, or photographic activities sponsored by Kodak. The novels listed were acquired by Mr. Ellis in order to document the unauthorized use of the Kodak trade name. Arranged in original order.
  - Contents of Box: (Box 82)
    - Proceedings of the Golden Anniversary Convention of the Photographers Association of America, 1930
    - Stereo Photography in Rochester NY up to 1900, 1975
    - The Gospel Kodak Abroad (novel), 1893
    - Down in Porto Rico With a Kodak (novel), 1898
    - Captain Kodak (novel), 1899
  - Contents of Box: (Box 83)
    - Publicités Kodak, 1910-1939, 1983
    - Invoices, 1910
    - Classroom Projects Using Photography, 1975
      - Part 1 - Elementary
      - Part 2 - Secondary
    - Hawk Eye Club Awards programs (25-year Kodak service club), 1952-1953
      Includes handwritten manuscript of presentation speech by President J. Kowalski.
    - Kodak Park 50 Years Ago: A Boy's Eye View of 1904, [1954?]
    - 20 Years of the Kodak Camera Club of Rochester, 1940
    - Program from Army-Navy Production award presentation, 1942
    - The American Boy Photographer, undated
    - Photographic Mosaics: An Annual Record of Photographic Progress, 1888
- Marketing Samples and Promotional Materials Series, [189-?]-[198-?] and undated
  Wide variety of Kodak artifacts such as samples books, albums, and promotional novelties. Arranged in original order.
  - Contents of Box: (Box 84)
    - Velox books (sample black and white photographs), undated, (3 items)
    - Photographic paper samples book, 1953
    - Kodak Portfolio: Sample black and white photographs from exhibition, 1897
    - Album of Dekko prints ( black and white photographs shot with various Kodak cameras), [189-]
  - Contents of Box: (Box 85)
    - Kodak photo albums, [circa 1939], [195-], and undated, (4 items)
  - Contents of Box: (Box 86)
    - Negative book, 1929
    - Empty photo album, undated
    - Empty negative book, undated
    - Photo album, 1902
  - Contents of Box: (Box 87)
    - Sample packaging/film processing envelopes, photos printed as promotional materials, [189?]-[192?], (76 items)
  - Contents of Box: (Box 88)
    - Novelties